CHUNGKANG CHOI

Software Developer

CONTACT

Email: chungkang.c@gmail.com

Phone: +82) 10 5433 1849

Address: Seoul, Republic of Korea

Linked In:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ck-c

SUMMARY

A software developer with a passion for geoinformatics. I've experienced the full process of software engineering with 2 years and a half of my professional software developer experience. Currently, I am conducting in depth learning on QGIS, Python, and data analysis to adapt a geographic information system.

SKILLS

Programming Languages

Java : 3 years JavaScript : 3 years SQL : 3 years Python : 1 year

Other Skills

Spring, jQuery, Django, React.js, AWS, SVN, Git, Travis CI

LANGUAGES

Korean: Native Japanes: C2 English: B2 German: B1

PROFESSIONAL CAREER

FSK L&S | Software Developer

September 2019 - March 2021

FSK L&S offers 'Logistics Business Process Outsourcing Services' with integrated logistics platform system "KEROL"

- Charged on forwarding system development and system maintenance
- Consulted, analysed and designed with customer requirements
- Developed and integrated API (with customer's ERP system, express company system)
- Analysed data on logistics platform for extracting KPI and other purposes
- Wrote technical documents such as user requirement specification, function specification, user guide, ERD
- Spring, MariaDB, jQuery, AWS, jenkins, Vue.js, Jira, SVN

Crespeed | Software Programmer

August 2018 - May 2019

Crespeed offers ERP system

- Programmed finance & accounting module of ERP system
- Wrote technical documents such as user requirement specification and user guide
- Converted ERP system Delphi to Java
- · Spring, Oracle, jQuery, SVN

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Korea National Open University

BSc Computer Scicence

March 2019 - February 2021

Seoul, Republic of Korea | GPA: 3.5 (1.8 in German Grade)

Chung-Ang University

BA Japanese Language and Literature BEc Marketing and Logistics Management

March 2012 - August 2018

Seoul, Republic of Korea | GPA: 3.49 (1.8 in German Grade)

CERTIFICATES

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

Amazon Web Services | September 2020

OCJP

Oracle | May 2018

Engineering Information Processing

Human Resources Development Service of Korea | May 2018